<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LangChain on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/langchain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LangChain on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/langchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #203</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-203/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-203/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. As always, more great new projects are featured in this edition, #203. Projects to check out include: how you can proxy OpenAI requests through Amazon Bedrock, security tools that help you stay one step ahead of bad actors, a way of implementing CDK Pipelines in a less opinionated way, a tool that helps you validate your AWS IAM policies, a toolkit to help get you started with good practices when creating CloudFormation templates, some demo code that demonstrate how you can implement zero downtime updates to your applications, as well as some really cool demos and use cases of generative AI in action (too many to mention, so check them all out!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #201</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-201/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-201/</guid>
      <description>Edition #201 Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, issue #201, your trusted source for the very best open source on AWS content. This weeks new projects for you to practice your four freedoms include generative AI infused projects to help you generate your docs, streamline the setting up of your AWS resources, a new experimental framework for building document based workflows, and a cool demo that showcases how you can use generative AI to help translate American Sign Language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #199</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-199/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-199/</guid>
      <description>Edition #199 Welcome to issue #199 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. I cannot believe that we are one issue away from a pretty significant milestone. I would love to hear from some of the regular readers of this newsletter to find any highlights they have had, or perhaps things they have found that have been pretty significant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #197</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-197/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-197/</guid>
      <description>Edition #197 Welcome to issue #197 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content.&#xA;Like in previous editions of this newsletter, we feature new projects for you you practice your four freedoms. We have some great projects, including a sprinkling of repos that look to help you benchmark and assess your generative AI models and agents, a new fruity framework for building document understanding applications, a nice container command line tool that sysadmins will love, a tool to help you migrate your CodeCommit repositories, a really nice application of using generative AI to help automate CVE findings, and a neat generative AI newsletter generation demo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #196</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-196/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-196/</guid>
      <description>Edition #196 Welcome to issue #196 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content.&#xA;As always, more great new projects are featured in this edition of the newsletter, including a link to the Valkey repo, a nice GUI based project to help you build orchestration workflows that uses Apache Airflow under the covers, a tool to help you find signals through the noise of your security logs, a project to help you run serverless tasks in a cron like fashion, a command line runner for Amazon CodeCatalyst, a tool to help you simplify the deployment of Cruise Control on Amazon MSK, a nice Mac client for experimenting with Amazon Bedrock, and some really cool demo apps, the pick of which (for me) is a nice way of surfacing up your Amazon Bedrock models in a way that existing applications that expect an API key can use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #195</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-195/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-195/</guid>
      <description>Edition #195 Welcome to issue #195 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. This week I am heading out to Everything Open, and looking forward to meeting the community in Gladstone. I will be talking about Cedar, and showing why it is important and how it works (demo is working lovely now). I am now on the third week of my open source roadshow, which is why I have had to change the publishing of this newsletter to every other week - at least until I get back home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #186</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-186/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-186/</guid>
      <description>Edition #186 Welcome to issue #186 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content.&#xA;As always, this week we start with a round up of some freshly baked new projects for you to practice your four freedoms. This week we have dashboards to help you cut through the noise when reviewing security information, a synthetic data generator that leverages generative AI, a tool to help you mask data from production so you can use it in development and testing, a solution to help you run VSCode on EC2, a tool to help you wipe your S3 Glacier data vaults, and an assortment of generative AI demos for you to try out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #184</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-184/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-184/</guid>
      <description>Edition #184 Welcome to issue #184 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content.&#xA;As always, this week we start with a round up of some freshly baked new projects for you to practice your four freedoms. This week we have a rust based cli tools to help you accelerate your S3 searches, we take a look at a new framework to help simplify bootstrapping your projects, a tool to help you report on your AWS resource tags, a voice translator for Chime, a really nice sample project to help you get hands on with Cedar, a number of generative AI demos and sample projects that are a must, and many more projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #181</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-181/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-181/</guid>
      <description>November 27th, 2023 - Instalment #181 Welcome to #181 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. As some of you will know, this is re:Invent week, where many of my colleagues and tens of thousands of developers will be congregating to learn about Cloud, and hopefully discover plenty of open source goodness too. If you are going, make sure to visit the open source booth in the Expo floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #180</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-180/</guid>
      <description>November 20th, 2023 - Instalment #180 Welcome to #180 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. As we ramp up to re:Invent, it is good to see that pre:Invent is giving us plenty of open source goodies. In this weeks newsletter, we have some of those in the way of new projects such as res and aws-iatk, but we also have lots of really great content too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #179</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-179/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-179/</guid>
      <description>November 13th, 2023 - Instalment #179 Welcome to #179 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. This weeks new projects include an open source tool that provides similar capabilities to AWS Control Tower, a tool for enrolling your Mac based EC2 instances into mobile device management (MDM) solution, a very neat tool to help you compare costs of running your CodePipeline jobs, as well as sample code that shows you how you can use Karpenter to optimise IP address use, examples of using Test Containers with AWS CDK, generative AI technologies such as LangChain, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #178</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-178/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-178/</guid>
      <description>November 6th, 2023 - Instalment #178 Welcome to #178 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. This week we feature more new open source projects for you to practice your four freedoms. We have a useful tool that helps you synchronise your AWS Identity Centre users with the users you provision in your Amazon RDS databases, we share the AWS data solutions framework that helps you build data solutions following opinionated best practices, a resource explorer for your AWS accounts, a guardrails solution for your AWS account, and a couple of demo repositories that take a look at Localstack and RSS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #176</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</guid>
      <description>October 23rd, 2023 - Instalment #176 Welcome to #176 of the AWS open source newsletter, heading into Autumn and getting ready for the clocks to go back later in the week. How will you use that extra hour? Well, perhaps some of you might use it to check out this weeks new projects, which include a nice cli chat tool that uses Amazon Bedrock, a tool to help simplify deploying VSCode in the Cloud environments, and sample demos and code on chaos engineering, deploying Amazon Bedrock via AWS Lambda, and how you can use IAM Roles Anywhere to authenticate against external identity providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #167</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-167/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-167/</guid>
      <description>July 31st, 2023 - Instalment #167 Welcome to #167 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another edition packed with new open source projects for you to explore. Whether you are new to this newsletter, or returning (we thank you!) there is something for you. This week we have projects that will help use Terraform to deploy your monolith applications, a tool to accelerate your GraphQL building when working with Amazon DynamoDB, a project that will help you introduce chaos without changes to your code, and a couple of really nice demos of using generative AI that allows you to use natural language to query your data.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
