<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ROSA on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/rosa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ROSA on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/rosa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #204</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-204/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-204/</guid>
      <description>Edition #204 Welcome to issue #204 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. Apologies for the long wait since the last edition, I will have to do better. Thanks for the lovely messages and feedback I have received over the past few weeks, this edition is for you!&#xA;As always, we have more great new projects to check out, which include projects that surface up your AWS costs in Home Assistant, a tool that you can use to ask questions about your code base that uses generative AI, a git large file storage (LFS) extension that lets you use Amazon S3, and a handy network cost calculator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #202</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-202/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-202/</guid>
      <description>Edition #202 Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, issue #202. In this edition, I share more new projects (thank you for those of you that have sent them through) which include a project to help you monitor your data pipelines, the open sourced AWS Secrets Manager agent, a really cool new framework for managing multi generative AI agents, a couple of interesting projects to help manage your AWS accounts, a repo that provides CloudFormation snippets, and a few demo applications including one I put together that shows how you can use the Amazon Bedrock Converse API to summarise Hacker News comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #200</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-200/</guid>
      <description>Edition #200 Welcome to a milestone edition of this newsletter, number #200!! Wow, it feels like quite an achievement. Before diving into this newsletter, a big thank you for sticking with me. Time has flown by so quickly, and am looking forward to the next 100. As I have done in a few of the previous milestone issues, I wanted to share a few interesting stats from sharing open source projects with you over the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #186</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-186/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-186/</guid>
      <description>Edition #186 Welcome to issue #186 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content.&#xA;As always, this week we start with a round up of some freshly baked new projects for you to practice your four freedoms. This week we have dashboards to help you cut through the noise when reviewing security information, a synthetic data generator that leverages generative AI, a tool to help you mask data from production so you can use it in development and testing, a solution to help you run VSCode on EC2, a tool to help you wipe your S3 Glacier data vaults, and an assortment of generative AI demos for you to try out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #185</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-185/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-185/</guid>
      <description>Edition #185 Welcome to issue #185 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content.&#xA;As always, this week we start with a round up of some freshly baked new projects for you to practice your four freedoms. This week we have projects that allow you to export your Partyrock applications, a tool to help you reduce hallucinations in your large language models, a new client for Redis, a tool to help you access the AWS Partner Network, as well as sample projects that look at how you can use large langue models to build a new reader and building pipelines using Cloudformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #155</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-155/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-155/</guid>
      <description>May 1st, 2023 - Instalment #155 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #155, the newsletter that just keeps on giving&amp;hellip;.in this case, keeps giving you brand new open source projects to practice your four freedoms on. This week&amp;rsquo;s new projects include&#xA;&amp;ldquo;aws-cloudformation-controller-for-flux&amp;rdquo; provides a way to use flux to orchestrate your CloudFormation deployments, &amp;ldquo;threat-composer&amp;rdquo; is a nice React based tool to help you create Threat Models for your systems and applications, &amp;ldquo;cdk-integ-tests-sample&amp;rdquo; a tool to allow you to do integration tests with your CDK stacks (these three were all featured in the latest episode of Build on Open Source, you can watch it here), &amp;ldquo;iam-access-key-report&amp;rdquo; generates reports from your AWS accounts about your AWS access keys, &amp;ldquo;personalize-kafka-connector&amp;rdquo; provides an integration into Apache Kafka for this AWS service, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #143</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</guid>
      <description>January 30th, 2023 - Instalment #143 Welcome to edition #143 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. This week we feature projects including &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-in-electron&amp;rdquo;, a project that lets you put AWS CDK in a graphical user interface, &amp;ldquo;lightsail-k8s-installer&amp;rdquo; that helps you deploy Kubernetes into Amazon Lightsail, &amp;ldquo;porting-advisor-for-graviton&amp;rdquo; a great project to help you migrate to Arm based AWS Graviton instance types, &amp;ldquo;aws-ebook-downloader&amp;rdquo; a browser tool to help you easily download pdf&amp;rsquo;s on AWS topics, &amp;ldquo;lake-formation-permissions-sync&amp;rdquo; a useful tool to help you keep on top of your Lake Formation setups, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #123</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</guid>
      <description>August, 5th, 2022 - Instalment #123 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter episode #123.&#xA;I sometimes speak with builders who are experienced developers but perhaps new to open source. A common question I get asked is what the impact of them working on open source might be on their careers. Whilst it is never a guarantee, open source can be a great career accelerator. I was reminded of that last week when reading the excellent post from Ran Isenberg, who shared his experience in his post How One Open-Source Code Donation Got Me Promoted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #113</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-113/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-113/</guid>
      <description>May 13th, 2022 - Instalment #113 Newsletter #113.&#xA;A little later than usual this week thanks to KubeCon, #113 of the AWS open source newsletter provides you with yet more new open source projects. &amp;ldquo;aws-iam-utils&amp;rdquo; is a Python library to help you work with IAM, &amp;ldquo;iot-app-kit&amp;rdquo; is a new IoT visualisation framework, &amp;ldquo;s3pathlib-project&amp;rdquo; that provides the Pythonic objective oriented programming (OOP) interface to manipulate AWS S3 object / directory, &amp;ldquo;collaboration-chambers-on-aws&amp;rdquo; which is a cool and very comprehensive project to help you do Scale-Out Computing on AWS, and many more!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
