<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PySpark on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/pyspark/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PySpark on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/pyspark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #196</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-196/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-196/</guid>
      <description>Edition #196 Welcome to issue #196 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content.&#xA;As always, more great new projects are featured in this edition of the newsletter, including a link to the Valkey repo, a nice GUI based project to help you build orchestration workflows that uses Apache Airflow under the covers, a tool to help you find signals through the noise of your security logs, a project to help you run serverless tasks in a cron like fashion, a command line runner for Amazon CodeCatalyst, a tool to help you simplify the deployment of Cruise Control on Amazon MSK, a nice Mac client for experimenting with Amazon Bedrock, and some really cool demo apps, the pick of which (for me) is a nice way of surfacing up your Amazon Bedrock models in a way that existing applications that expect an API key can use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #192</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-192/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-192/</guid>
      <description>Edition #192 Welcome to issue #192 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. As always, this week we start with a round up of some freshly baked new projects for you to practice your four freedoms. A wide variety this week, and we have projects that help you create architecture diagrams from your YAML, visualise and create dashboards for compliance and reporting purposes, a new multi-cloud threat detection tool, a Go implementation of Cedar, an example of load testing your large language models, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #179</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-179/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-179/</guid>
      <description>November 13th, 2023 - Instalment #179 Welcome to #179 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. This weeks new projects include an open source tool that provides similar capabilities to AWS Control Tower, a tool for enrolling your Mac based EC2 instances into mobile device management (MDM) solution, a very neat tool to help you compare costs of running your CodePipeline jobs, as well as sample code that shows you how you can use Karpenter to optimise IP address use, examples of using Test Containers with AWS CDK, generative AI technologies such as LangChain, and more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
