<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OpenTelemetry on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/opentelemetry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OpenTelemetry on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/opentelemetry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #203</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-203/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-203/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. As always, more great new projects are featured in this edition, #203. Projects to check out include: how you can proxy OpenAI requests through Amazon Bedrock, security tools that help you stay one step ahead of bad actors, a way of implementing CDK Pipelines in a less opinionated way, a tool that helps you validate your AWS IAM policies, a toolkit to help get you started with good practices when creating CloudFormation templates, some demo code that demonstrate how you can implement zero downtime updates to your applications, as well as some really cool demos and use cases of generative AI in action (too many to mention, so check them all out!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #198</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-198/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-198/</guid>
      <description>Edition #198 Welcome to issue #198 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. In this issue we feature new projects that provide integration of .NET Aspire with AWS resources, an automated data discovery tool to find data in your AWS environments, a tool to help incorporate good practices when building SaaS solutions, a cost allocation dashboard for your Kubernetes workloads, a project that might help you mitigate costs around Internet Gateway, and a few generative AI demos around food, news, and social media which you should definitely check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #193</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-193/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-193/</guid>
      <description>Edition #193 Welcome to issue #193 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. Sadly I will be missing the fun at KubeCon in Paris, but if you are attending, make sure to check out the AWS booth - I had a sneak peak at what you can expect, and there is going to be some great demos being shown, a lot of our open source folk will be there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #191</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-191/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-191/</guid>
      <description>Edition #191 Welcome to issue #191 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. As always, this week we start with a round up of some freshly baked new projects for you to practice your four freedoms. This week we have projects that cover AWS Nitro Enclaves, open source mapping libraries, how to grab secrets into your application configuration files, database performance benchmarking and analysis, improving the logging your applications generate, and a number of very handy tools to help you manage security data from the command line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #183</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-183/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-183/</guid>
      <description>January 8th, 2024 - Instalment #183 Happy new year and welcome to the first edition of the AWS open source newsletter of 2024, number #183. The big news for 2024 is the move from dev.to to community.aws as the &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo; for the AWS open source newsletter, although it will still be posted on dev.to as well. Let me know what you think, community.aws has some top notch content that many readers might not be aware of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #174</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-174/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-174/</guid>
      <description>September 18th, 2023 - Instalment #174 Welcome to #174 of the AWS open source newsletter, which will be the last one for a couple of weeks as I take some time off to recharge. I will be back in early October with more open source goodness, but in the meantime, you still have this edition packed with open source goodness.&#xA;This weeks new projects include a Rust tool to help you keep your CloudFormation stacks up to date, a tool to help upload files to Amazon S3, a generative AI tool that aims to help you review and detect IAM configuration issues, an updated JDBC driver for connecting to Amazon Aurora, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #158</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</guid>
      <description>May 30th, 2023 - Instalment #158 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #158. I hope some of you were able to catch the last episode of season two of Build on Open Source where we looked at some of the projects featured in this newsletter (specctl, eksdemo, and ec2-spot-placement-score-tracker). As always we pride ourself on this newsletter on giving you the newest, shiniest open source projects and this week we have some really great ones to share with you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #97</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-97/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-97/</guid>
      <description>Jan 22nd, 2022 - Instalment #97 Newsletter #97.&#xA;Welcome to another edition of the AWS open source newsletter, packed with more great new open source projects, content, and events. This week, we have new projects that help you improve security by de-obfuscating strings, a library to help you automate the configuration of your build pipelines, a new Terraform module, a nice new VSCode plugin that will help you when working with IAM, and several more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
