<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DeeQu on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/deequ/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DeeQu on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/deequ/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #204</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-204/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-204/</guid>
      <description>Edition #204 Welcome to issue #204 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. Apologies for the long wait since the last edition, I will have to do better. Thanks for the lovely messages and feedback I have received over the past few weeks, this edition is for you!&#xA;As always, we have more great new projects to check out, which include projects that surface up your AWS costs in Home Assistant, a tool that you can use to ask questions about your code base that uses generative AI, a git large file storage (LFS) extension that lets you use Amazon S3, and a handy network cost calculator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #203</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-203/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-203/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. As always, more great new projects are featured in this edition, #203. Projects to check out include: how you can proxy OpenAI requests through Amazon Bedrock, security tools that help you stay one step ahead of bad actors, a way of implementing CDK Pipelines in a less opinionated way, a tool that helps you validate your AWS IAM policies, a toolkit to help get you started with good practices when creating CloudFormation templates, some demo code that demonstrate how you can implement zero downtime updates to your applications, as well as some really cool demos and use cases of generative AI in action (too many to mention, so check them all out!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #160</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-160/</guid>
      <description>June 12th, 2023 - Instalment #160 Welcome to #160 of the AWS open source newsletter, where we try and share all the important open source news, projects, events, and content that open source builders want. This week we have new projects that include tools to help you build data workflows, Terraform modules to help you incorporate temporary elevated access controls, integrating Tailscale to change your traffic flows, a neat AWS Lambda debugging tool, Go bindings for Cedar, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #138</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</guid>
      <description>December 12th, 2022 - Instalment #138 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #138. After a week off due to re:Invent, this edition is packed with content on many of the open source related announcements. As always, we have a great line up of new projects for you to practice your four freedoms on. In no particular order, we have projects like &amp;ldquo;eks-node-viewer&amp;rdquo;, a nice visualisation tool for your Amazon EKS clusters, &amp;ldquo;pg_tle&amp;rdquo; a great new project to make your PostgreSQL environments safer, &amp;ldquo;dyna53&amp;rdquo; a fun project that finally turns Amazon Route 53 into a database, &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-mass-migrations&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you migrate to Amazon DynamoDB, &amp;ldquo;visual-asset-management-system&amp;rdquo; a very nice digital asset management tool, &amp;ldquo;fast-differential-privacy&amp;rdquo; implement differential privacy in your PyTorch models, &amp;ldquo;migration-hadoop-to-emr-tco-simulator&amp;rdquo; a handy total cost of ownership calculator for Amazon EMR, &amp;ldquo;realtime-toxicity-detection&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you stay on top of your online communities, &amp;ldquo;functionclarity&amp;rdquo; a very cool tool to check the integrity of your serverless functions before executing, and many more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
