<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>InfluxDB on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/influxdb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in InfluxDB on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/influxdb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #204</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-204/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-204/</guid>
      <description>Edition #204 Welcome to issue #204 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. Apologies for the long wait since the last edition, I will have to do better. Thanks for the lovely messages and feedback I have received over the past few weeks, this edition is for you!&#xA;As always, we have more great new projects to check out, which include projects that surface up your AWS costs in Home Assistant, a tool that you can use to ask questions about your code base that uses generative AI, a git large file storage (LFS) extension that lets you use Amazon S3, and a handy network cost calculator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #202</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-202/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-202/</guid>
      <description>Edition #202 Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, issue #202. In this edition, I share more new projects (thank you for those of you that have sent them through) which include a project to help you monitor your data pipelines, the open sourced AWS Secrets Manager agent, a really cool new framework for managing multi generative AI agents, a couple of interesting projects to help manage your AWS accounts, a repo that provides CloudFormation snippets, and a few demo applications including one I put together that shows how you can use the Amazon Bedrock Converse API to summarise Hacker News comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #198</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-198/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-198/</guid>
      <description>Edition #198 Welcome to issue #198 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. In this issue we feature new projects that provide integration of .NET Aspire with AWS resources, an automated data discovery tool to find data in your AWS environments, a tool to help incorporate good practices when building SaaS solutions, a cost allocation dashboard for your Kubernetes workloads, a project that might help you mitigate costs around Internet Gateway, and a few generative AI demos around food, news, and social media which you should definitely check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #194</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-194/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-194/</guid>
      <description>Edition #194 Welcome to issue #194 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. Due to travelling and speaking commitments, regular readers will have noticed that I slipped up and missed a week. Normal service has been resumed, and as always, this week we start with a round up of some freshly baked new projects for you to practice your four freedoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #193</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-193/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-193/</guid>
      <description>Edition #193 Welcome to issue #193 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. Sadly I will be missing the fun at KubeCon in Paris, but if you are attending, make sure to check out the AWS booth - I had a sneak peak at what you can expect, and there is going to be some great demos being shown, a lot of our open source folk will be there.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
