<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Istio on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/istio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Istio on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/istio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #197</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-197/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-197/</guid>
      <description>Edition #197 Welcome to issue #197 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content.&#xA;Like in previous editions of this newsletter, we feature new projects for you you practice your four freedoms. We have some great projects, including a sprinkling of repos that look to help you benchmark and assess your generative AI models and agents, a new fruity framework for building document understanding applications, a nice container command line tool that sysadmins will love, a tool to help you migrate your CodeCommit repositories, a really nice application of using generative AI to help automate CVE findings, and a neat generative AI newsletter generation demo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #193</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-193/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-193/</guid>
      <description>Edition #193 Welcome to issue #193 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. Sadly I will be missing the fun at KubeCon in Paris, but if you are attending, make sure to check out the AWS booth - I had a sneak peak at what you can expect, and there is going to be some great demos being shown, a lot of our open source folk will be there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #192</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-192/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-192/</guid>
      <description>Edition #192 Welcome to issue #192 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. As always, this week we start with a round up of some freshly baked new projects for you to practice your four freedoms. A wide variety this week, and we have projects that help you create architecture diagrams from your YAML, visualise and create dashboards for compliance and reporting purposes, a new multi-cloud threat detection tool, a Go implementation of Cedar, an example of load testing your large language models, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #184</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-184/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-184/</guid>
      <description>Edition #184 Welcome to issue #184 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content.&#xA;As always, this week we start with a round up of some freshly baked new projects for you to practice your four freedoms. This week we have a rust based cli tools to help you accelerate your S3 searches, we take a look at a new framework to help simplify bootstrapping your projects, a tool to help you report on your AWS resource tags, a voice translator for Chime, a really nice sample project to help you get hands on with Cedar, a number of generative AI demos and sample projects that are a must, and many more projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #183</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-183/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-183/</guid>
      <description>January 8th, 2024 - Instalment #183 Happy new year and welcome to the first edition of the AWS open source newsletter of 2024, number #183. The big news for 2024 is the move from dev.to to community.aws as the &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo; for the AWS open source newsletter, although it will still be posted on dev.to as well. Let me know what you think, community.aws has some top notch content that many readers might not be aware of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #181</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-181/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-181/</guid>
      <description>November 27th, 2023 - Instalment #181 Welcome to #181 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. As some of you will know, this is re:Invent week, where many of my colleagues and tens of thousands of developers will be congregating to learn about Cloud, and hopefully discover plenty of open source goodness too. If you are going, make sure to visit the open source booth in the Expo floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #175</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</guid>
      <description>October 16th, 2023 - Instalment #175 Welcome to #175 of the AWS open source newsletter, back after recharging in the wonderful countyside of Yorkshire. I am publishing this weeks newsletter from Raleigh, North Carolina. All Things Open is happening this week, and you will catch me at the AWS booth where I will be showing off some cool open source stuff (Cedar, Apache Airflow, and a few others), and I also have a talk on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #112</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-112/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-112/</guid>
      <description>May 13th, 2022 - Instalment #112 Newsletter #112.&#xA;Welcome to this weeks round up of AWS open source news. This weeks new projects features projects such as &amp;ldquo;aws-dataall&amp;rdquo; an open source framework for building a data marketplace, &amp;ldquo;backpack&amp;rdquo; a set of tools to help you work with the AWS Panorama devices, and we have other projects that help you automate DNS tasks, manage game servers, automate data ingestion, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #110</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-110/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-110/</guid>
      <description>April 29th, 2022 - Instalment #110 Newsletter #110.&#xA;Welcome to edition #110 of the AWS open source newsletter. It has been a busy week, with the AWS Summit London happening this week (where I was lucky enough to do a session on Apache Airflow) meaning I am publishing this a little later than I had planned. We have more great new projects this week, including a project that helps make it easier to deploy your static and dynamic applications, a tool that provides help in managing the long term health of your AWS Data Lake, a cool project to help you replicate data from a Kinesis Data Stream across regions, a nice CloudWatch dashboard widget that summarises your CloudFormation stacks, and many more - so check them out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #109</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-109/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-109/</guid>
      <description>April 22nd, 2022 - Instalment #109 Newsletter #109.&#xA;Welcome to edition #109 of the AWS open source newsletter. Big news, I have shaken things up and will be changing the publish date to Friday mornings, starting today with this edition. Over the months I have received some feedback about changing the published date to Fridays, so I am hoping this will give everyone plenty of time to check out the projects, read the posts and provide everyone with something to do over the weekend (if they want!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
