<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ActiveMQ on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/activemq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ActiveMQ on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/activemq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #203</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-203/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-203/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter where we try and provide you the best open source on AWS content. As always, more great new projects are featured in this edition, #203. Projects to check out include: how you can proxy OpenAI requests through Amazon Bedrock, security tools that help you stay one step ahead of bad actors, a way of implementing CDK Pipelines in a less opinionated way, a tool that helps you validate your AWS IAM policies, a toolkit to help get you started with good practices when creating CloudFormation templates, some demo code that demonstrate how you can implement zero downtime updates to your applications, as well as some really cool demos and use cases of generative AI in action (too many to mention, so check them all out!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #183</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-183/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-183/</guid>
      <description>January 8th, 2024 - Instalment #183 Happy new year and welcome to the first edition of the AWS open source newsletter of 2024, number #183. The big news for 2024 is the move from dev.to to community.aws as the &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo; for the AWS open source newsletter, although it will still be posted on dev.to as well. Let me know what you think, community.aws has some top notch content that many readers might not be aware of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #163</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-163/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-163/</guid>
      <description>July 3rd, 2023 - Instalment #163 Welcome to #163 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week. This weeks featured projects include a Cedar authorisation service and demo examples, a tool to help you find dangling DNS records, a new CLI for those using Amazon ECR, an accelerator for observability on AWS, a serverless web analytics solution (so good, that I implemented it myself), and several more projects.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
